onlinejobsjunction.com 2016-11-25

# Online Jobs from Home, Online Survey Jobs, Part time online jobs

PRIVACY POLICY  
We, at OnlineJobsJunction.com thank you for trusting us with your personal information. We respect your privacy and are committed to safe use of information shared by you.

This web site collects online contact information in two ways, registration form, and enquiry forms submitted through contact us page. The information collected may be used to send the user information about our website or to get in touch with the user when necessary.

We respect your privacy and will not release your personal information to any organization without your consent. We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to any outside organizations. Any information you choose to give us is never shared with any other party.

OnlineJobsJunction.com does provide links to other sites. Other Internet sites and services have separate privacy and data collection practices. Once you leave OnlineJobsJunction.com, OnlineJobsJunction.com cannot control, and has no responsibility for, the privacy policies or data collection activities at another site.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at contact[at]OnlineJobsJunction.com

OnlineJobsJunction.com may from time to time revise its privacy policy. You should therefore periodically visit this page, so you are aware of any such revisions.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy and/or the practices of our web site, you can contact us at contact[at]OnlineJobsJunction.com
